<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>child-only on oot.wiki</title>
    <link>https://oot.wiki/tags/child-only/</link>
    <description>Recent content in child-only on oot.wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://oot.wiki/tags/child-only/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>B1 Skip</title>
      <link>https://oot.wiki/docs/deku-tree/b1-skip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oot.wiki/docs/deku-tree/b1-skip/</guid>
      <description>B1 Skip    Description A B1 Skip is any way to reach the higher platform in the basement of the Deku Tree starting from the water as child.
Applications This skips four rooms in B1 including a Slingshot-locked room, allowing the player to reach Gohma without having the Slingshot.
This trick is considered essential in randomizers as it skips an item requirement and saves a few minutes of going through empty rooms (except for one Gold Skulltula).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broken Deku Stick</title>
      <link>https://oot.wiki/docs/generic/broken-deku-stick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oot.wiki/docs/generic/broken-deku-stick/</guid>
      <description>Broken Deku Stick    Description Broken Deku Stick is a glitch that allows using a broken Deku Stick after breaking it, meaning you can indefinitely and rapidly output Master Sword level damage as child without ever having to obtain the Kokiri Sword.
The glitch occurs when a Deku Stick hits two times in a single jump-slash and will stay activated until the item in Link&amp;rsquo;s hand is replaced or a Scene transition occurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gohma One Cycle</title>
      <link>https://oot.wiki/docs/deku-tree/gohma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oot.wiki/docs/deku-tree/gohma/</guid>
      <description>Gohma One Cycle    Description This one-cycle allows you to defeat Gohma in under five seconds.
Setup This setup requires two Deku Sticks one of which will be consumed, and one Deku Nut.
 After getting through the door, perform the Broken Deku Stick glitch on a wall. After Gohma drops to the floor, go closer to it and throw a Deku Nut with your C-Buttons Power Crouch Stab once While the animation of the previous attack is still playing, start spamming your C-Buttons to throw another Deku Nut.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>